{
    "N3L1VQuiz": [
        { "question": "completion / to finish", "kanji_question": "完了", "answer": "かんりょう" },
        { "question": "procedure", "kanji_question": "手続き", "answer": "てつづき" },
        { "question": "return / to return", "kanji_question": "返却", "answer": "へんきゃく" },
        { "question": "lending", "kanji_question": "貸し出し", "answer": "かしだし" },
        { "question": "issue / to issue", "kanji_question": "発行", "answer": "はっこう" },
        { "question": "reissue / to reissue", "kanji_question": "再発行", "answer": "さいはっこう" },
        { "question": "possibility / possible", "kanji_question": "可能", "answer": "かのう" },
        { "question": "situation", "kanji_question": "状況", "answer": "じょうきょう" },
        { "question": "strange / funny / weird / odd / ridiculous", "kanji_question": "可笑しい", "answer": "おかしい" },
        { "question": "start of business hours / to be open", "kanji_question": "開館", "answer": "かいかん" },
        { "question": "end of business hours / to be closed", "kanji_question": "閉館", "answer": "へいかん" },
        { "question": "closed period / to be closed for the day", "kanji_question": "休館", "answer": "きゅうかん" },
        { "question": "days closed", "kanji_question": "休館日", "answer": "きゅうかんび" },
        { "question": "weekdays", "kanji_question": "平日", "answer": "へいじつ" },
        { "question": "national holiday", "kanji_question": "祝日", "answer": "しゅくじつ" },
        { "question": "Year-end and New Year holidays", "kanji_question": "年末年始", "answer": "ねんまつねんし" },
        { "question": "guidance / to guide", "kanji_question": "案内", "answer": "あんない" },
        { "question": "the next day", "kanji_question": "翌日", "answer": "よくじつ" },
        { "question": "the previous day", "kanji_question": "前日", "answer": "ぜんじつ" },
        { "question": "use / to use", "kanji_question": "使用", "answer": "しよう" },
        { "question": "content", "kanji_question": "内容", "answer": "ないよう" },
        { "question": "child", "kanji_question": "児童", "answer": "じどう" },
        { "question": "adult", "kanji_question": "大人", "answer": "おとな" },
        { "question": "city", "kanji_question": "都市", "answer": "とし" },
        { "question": "citizen", "kanji_question": "市民", "answer": "しみん" },
        { "question": "furthermore / yet", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "なお" },
        { "question": "however", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ただし" },
        { "question": "free of charge / ordinary / only / but", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ただ" },
        { "question": "construction", "kanji_question": "工事", "answer": "こうじ" },
        { "question": "form", "kanji_question": "用紙", "answer": "ようし" },
        { "question": "filling out / to fill out", "kanji_question": "記入", "answer": "きにゅう" },
        { "question": "contact information", "kanji_question": "連絡先", "answer": "れんらくさき" },
        { "question": "submission / to submit", "kanji_question": "提出", "answer": "ていしゅつ" },
        { "question": "counter", "kanji_question": "窓口", "answer": "まどぐち" },
        { "question": "and", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "や" },
        { "question": "keep / to look after something", "kanji_question": "預かる", "answer": "あずかる" },
        { "question": "to leave something in somebody's care", "kanji_question": "預ける", "answer": "あずける" },
        { "question": "change / to change", "kanji_question": "変更", "answer": "へんこう" },
        { "question": "conversion / to convert", "kanji_question": "変換", "answer": "へんかん" },
        { "question": "development / to develop", "kanji_question": "開発", "answer": "かいはつ" },
        { "question": "one's identity", "kanji_question": "身分", "answer": "みぶん" },
        { "question": "identity document (ID)", "kanji_question": "身分証明書", "answer": "みぶんしょうめいしょ" },
        { "question": "salt", "kanji_question": "塩", "answer": "しお" },
        { "question": "report", "kanji_question": "報告", "answer": "ほうこく" },
        { "question": "a written report", "kanji_question": "報告書", "answer": "ほうこくしょ" },
        { "question": "iron", "kanji_question": "鉄", "answer": "てつ" },
        { "question": "to strike / to hit / to beat", "kanji_question": "打つ", "answer": "うつ" },
        { "question": "to chase", "kanji_question": "追いかける", "answer": "おいかける" },
        { "question": "coming to a store or a restaurant", "kanji_question": "来店", "answer": "らいてん" },
        { "question": "greatly / indeed", "kanji_question": "誠に", "answer": "まことに" },
        { "question": "mailbox", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ボスト" }
    ],
    "N3L2VQuiz": [
        { "question": "home delivery", "kanji_question": "宅配便", "answer": "たくはいびん" },
        { "question": "delivered goods", "kanji_question": "届け物", "answer": "とどけもの" },
        { "question": "product", "kanji_question": "商品", "answer": "しょうひん" },
        { "question": "sale / to sell", "kanji_question": "販売", "answer": "はんばい" },
        { "question": "mail order", "kanji_question": "通信販売", "answer": "つうしんはんばい" },
        { "question": "delivery / to deliver", "kanji_question": "配達", "answer": "はいたつ" },
        { "question": "high heels", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ハイヒール" },
        { "question": "sneakers", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "スニーカー" },
        { "question": "boots", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ブーツ" },
        { "question": "to notice", "kanji_question": "気付く", "answer": "きづく" },
        { "question": "to be anxious / to worry", "kanji_question": "気になる", "answer": "きになる" },
        { "question": "to mind / to worry", "kanji_question": "気にする", "answer": "きにする" },
        { "question": "to be pleased with", "kanji_question": "気に入る", "answer": "きにいる" },
        { "question": "to remember", "kanji_question": "思い出す", "answer": "おもいだす" },
        { "question": "hard / strong / stern / tight", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "きつい" },
        { "question": "to become dirty", "kanji_question": "汚れる", "answer": "よごれる" },
        { "question": "dirty", "kanji_question": "汚れ", "answer": "よごれ" },
        { "question": "returns / to return (goods)", "kanji_question": "返品", "answer": "へんぴん" },
        { "question": "exchange / to exchange (goods)", "kanji_question": "交換", "answer": "こうかん" },
        { "question": "New York", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ニューヨーク" },
        { "question": "Statue of Liberty", "kanji_question": "自由の女神", "answer": "じゆうのめがみ" },
        { "question": "to float", "kanji_question": "浮かぶ", "answer": "うかぶ" },
        { "question": "a town in Japan known for its hot springs", "kanji_question": "箱根", "answer": "はこね" },
        { "question": "opponent", "kanji_question": "相手", "answer": "あいて" },
        { "question": "resolution / to solve", "kanji_question": "解決", "answer": "かいけつ" },
        { "question": "to believe", "kanji_question": "信じる", "answer": "しんじる" },
        { "question": "trust / to trust / to rely on", "kanji_question": "信頼", "answer": "しんらい" },
        { "question": "trust / to trust / to confide in", "kanji_question": "信用", "answer": "しんよう" },
        { "question": "secret", "kanji_question": "秘密", "answer": "ひみつ" },
        { "question": "textbook", "kanji_question": "教科書", "answer": "きょうかしょ" },
        { "question": "ordinary / everyday", "kanji_question": "日常", "answer": "にちじょう" },
        { "question": "ingredients", "kanji_question": "食材", "answer": "しょくざい" },
        { "question": "quite / almost", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "まるで" },
        { "question": "doll", "kanji_question": "人形", "answer": "にんぎょう" },
        { "question": "to feel down", "kanji_question": "落ち込む", "answer": "おちこむ" },
        { "question": "to depend on", "kanji_question": "甘える", "answer": "あまえる" },
        { "question": "example", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "たとえ" },
        { "question": "midsummer", "kanji_question": "真夏", "answer": "まなつ" },
        { "question": "midwinter", "kanji_question": "真冬", "answer": "まふゆ" },
        { "question": "cow", "kanji_question": "牛", "answer": "うし" },
        { "question": "rabbit", "kanji_question": "兔", "answer": "うさぎ" },
        { "question": "mouse", "kanji_question": "鼠", "answer": "ねずみ" },
        { "question": "monkey", "kanji_question": "猿", "answer": "さる" },
        { "question": "demon / ghost", "kanji_question": "鬼", "answer": "おに" },
        { "question": "frightening", "kanji_question": "恐ろしい", "answer": "おそろしい" },
        { "question": "to fear", "kanji_question": "恐れる", "answer": "おそれる" },
        { "question": "dissatisfaction / dissatisfied", "kanji_question": "不満", "answer": "ふまん" },
        { "question": "satisfaction / to satisfy", "kanji_question": "満足", "answer": "まんぞく" },
        { "question": "conditions / terms", "kanji_question": "条件", "answer": "じょうけん" },
        { "question": "to satisfy / to fulfill", "kanji_question": "満たす", "answer": "みたす" },
        { "question": "about / regarding", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "について" },
        { "question": "to differ", "kanji_question": "異なる", "answer": "ことなる" },
        { "question": "a break / to have a rest", "kanji_question": "休憩", "answer": "きゅうけい" },
        { "question": "salary", "kanji_question": "給料", "answer": "きゅうりょう" },
        { "question": "tag", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "タグ" },
        { "question": "reason", "kanji_question": "理由", "answer": "りゆう" },
        { "question": "result", "kanji_question": "結果", "answer": "けっか" },
        { "question": "to contain", "kanji_question": "含む", "answer": "ふくむ" },
        { "question": "delivery of goods / to deliver goods to", "kanji_question": "納品", "answer": "のうひん" },
        { "question": "statement of delivery", "kanji_question": "納品書", "answer": "のうひんしょ" },
        { "question": "possibly / or", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "あるいは" },
        { "question": "to limit", "kanji_question": "限る", "answer": "かぎる" },
        { "question": "high resolution", "kanji_question": "高画質", "answer": "こうがしつ" },
        { "question": "coach", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "コーチ" },
        { "question": "chest", "kanji_question": "胸", "answer": "むね" },
        { "question": "entering a company / to enter a company", "kanji_question": "入社", "answer": "にゅうしゃ" }
    ],
    "N3L3VQuiz": [
        { "question": "advertisement / to advertise", "kanji_question": "広告", "answer": "こうこく" },
        { "question": "thesis / essay", "kanji_question": "論文", "answer": "ろんぶん" },
        { "question": "announcement / to announce", "kanji_question": "発表", "answer": "はっぴょう" },
        { "question": "resume", "kanji_question": "履歴書", "answer": "りれきしょ" },
        { "question": "interview / to interview", "kanji_question": "面接", "answer": "めんせつ" },
        { "question": "to respond / to accept / to comply", "kanji_question": "応じる", "answer": "おうじる" },
        { "question": "improvement / to improve / to progress", "kanji_question": "上達", "answer": "じょうたつ" },
        { "question": "in charge / to be in charge", "kanji_question": "担当", "answer": "たんとう" },
        { "question": "full time employee", "kanji_question": "正社員", "answer": "せいしゃいん" },
        { "question": "internship", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "インターンシップ" },
        { "question": "business / trade / sales / to do business", "kanji_question": "営業", "answer": "えいぎょう" },
        { "question": "hourly wage", "kanji_question": "時給", "answer": "じきゅう" },
        { "question": "consultation / to consult", "kanji_question": "相談", "answer": "そうだん" },
        { "question": "application / to apply / to subscribe", "kanji_question": "応募", "answer": "おうぼ" },
        { "question": "recruitment / to recruit", "kanji_question": "募集", "answer": "ぼしゅう" },
        { "question": "business / work", "kanji_question": "業務", "answer": "ぎょうむ" },
        { "question": "service / duty / to serve", "kanji_question": "勤務", "answer": "きんむ" },
        { "question": "workplace", "kanji_question": "勤務地", "answer": "きんむち" },
        { "question": "status / privilege / qualifications", "kanji_question": "資格", "answer": "しかく" },
        { "question": "experience / to experience", "kanji_question": "経験", "answer": "けいけん" },
        { "question": "experienced person", "kanji_question": "経験者", "answer": "けいけんしゃ" },
        { "question": "beginner", "kanji_question": "初心者", "answer": "しょしんしゃ" },
        { "question": "welcome / to welcome", "kanji_question": "歓迎", "answer": "かんげい" },
        { "question": "language study", "kanji_question": "語学", "answer": "ごがく" },
        { "question": "lovely / great / fantastic", "kanji_question": "素敵", "answer": "すてき" },
        { "question": "grace of / favor / thanks to", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "おかげ" },
        { "question": "cause", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "せい" },
        { "question": "politics", "kanji_question": "政治", "answer": "せいじ" },
        { "question": "argument / debate / to argue / to debate", "kanji_question": "議論", "answer": "ぎろん" },
        { "question": "professor / to teach", "kanji_question": "教授", "answer": "きょうじゅ" },
        { "question": "discovery / to discover", "kanji_question": "発見", "answer": "はっけん" },
        { "question": "license", "kanji_question": "免許", "answer": "めんきょ" },
        { "question": "area / region", "kanji_question": "地域", "answer": "ちいき" },
        { "question": "climate", "kanji_question": "気候", "answer": "きこう" },
        { "question": "lifetime / one's whole time", "kanji_question": "一生", "answer": "いっしょう" },
        { "question": "management / to manage", "kanji_question": "管理", "answer": "かんり" },
        { "question": "aid / support / to aid / to support", "kanji_question": "応援", "answer": "おうえん" },
        { "question": "victory / to win", "kanji_question": "優勝", "answer": "ゆうしょう" },
        { "question": "chocolate", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "チョコレート" },
        { "question": "temperature (weather)", "kanji_question": "気温", "answer": "きおん" },
        { "question": "secretly", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "こっそり" },
        { "question": "one's own car", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "マイカー" },
        { "question": "to be impressed / to be touched", "kanji_question": "感動", "answer": "かんどう" },
        { "question": "memory / recollection / to remember / to memorize", "kanji_question": "記憶", "answer": "きおく" },
        { "question": "sightseeing / tourism / to tour", "kanji_question": "観光", "answer": "かんこう" },
        { "question": "tourist", "kanji_question": "観光客", "answer": "かんこうきゃく" },
        { "question": "wonderful / splendid", "kanji_question": "素晴らしい", "answer": "すばらしい" },
        { "question": "boredom / boring / to be bored", "kanji_question": "退屈", "answer": "たいくつ" },
        { "question": "unexpected", "kanji_question": "意外", "answer": "いがい" },
        { "question": "luxury / luxurious / to be extravagant", "kanji_question": "贅沢", "answer": "ぜいたく" },
        { "question": "feeling / sense", "kanji_question": "感じ", "answer": "かんじ" },
        { "question": "to feel / to sense", "kanji_question": "感じる", "answer": "かんじる" },
        { "question": "to suit (something / someone)", "kanji_question": "似合う", "answer": "にあう" },
        { "question": "to grow / to stretch / to expand", "kanji_question": "伸びる", "answer": "のびる" },
        { "question": "to grow / to stretch / to expand (something)", "kanji_question": "伸ばす", "answer": "のばす" },
        { "question": "not yet / still / still more", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "まだまだ" },
        { "question": "high price / expensive", "kanji_question": "高価", "answer": "こうか" },
        { "question": "pollution / to pollute", "kanji_question": "汚染", "answer": "おせん" },
        { "question": "influence / effect / to influence / to affect", "kanji_question": "影響", "answer": "えいきょう" },
        { "question": "to give / to award / to bestow", "kanji_question": "与える", "answer": "あたえる" },
        { "question": "health / healthy", "kanji_question": "健康", "answer": "けんこう" },
        { "question": "poor health / unhealthy", "kanji_question": "不健康", "answer": "ふけんこう" },
        { "question": "theory", "kanji_question": "理論", "answer": "りろん" },
        { "question": "account / bill (payment)", "kanji_question": "会計", "answer": "かいけい" },
        { "question": "environment", "kanji_question": "環境", "answer": "かんきょう" },
        { "question": "real estate", "kanji_question": "不動産", "answer": "ふどうさん" },
        { "question": "reality / fact / really / in fact", "kanji_question": "実際", "answer": "じっさい" },
        { "question": "global environment", "kanji_question": "地球環境", "answer": "ちきゅうかんきょう" },
        { "question": "physics", "kanji_question": "物理", "answer": "ぶつり" },
        { "question": "sentence / composition / writing", "kanji_question": "文章", "answer": "ぶんしょう" },
        { "question": "invention / to invent", "kanji_question": "発明", "answer": "はつめい" }
    ],
    "N3L4VQuiz": [
        { "question": "Australia", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "オーストラリア" },
        { "question": "dormitory", "kanji_question": "寮", "answer": "りょう" },
        { "question": "(modern) apartment / condominium", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "マンション" },
        { "question": "(cheap / small) apartment", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "アパート" },
        { "question": "skyscraper", "kanji_question": "高層ビル", "answer": "こうそうビル" },
        { "question": "rule", "kanji_question": "規則", "answer": "きそく" },
        { "question": "center", "kanji_question": "中心", "answer": "ちゅうしん" },
        { "question": "number", "kanji_question": "数", "answer": "かず" },
        { "question": "kind / variety", "kanji_question": "種類", "answer": "しゅるい" },
        { "question": "proxy / representation", "kanji_question": "代理", "answer": "だいり" },
        { "question": "direction", "kanji_question": "向き", "answer": "むき" },
        { "question": "to turn toward", "kanji_question": "向く", "answer": "むく" },
        { "question": "to turn something toward", "kanji_question": "向ける", "answer": "むける" },
        { "question": "rainy season", "kanji_question": "梅雨", "answer": "つゆ" },
        { "question": "heavy rain", "kanji_question": "大雨", "answer": "おおあめ" },
        { "question": "heavy snow", "kanji_question": "大雪", "answer": "おおゆき" },
        { "question": "payment", "kanji_question": "支払い", "answer": "しはらい" },
        { "question": "to pay", "kanji_question": "支払う", "answer": "しはらう" },
        { "question": "resident", "kanji_question": "住民", "answer": "じゅうみん" },
        { "question": "anxious / anxiety", "kanji_question": "不安", "answer": "ふあん" },
        { "question": "bathtub / bathroom", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "バス" },
        { "question": "free", "kanji_question": "無料", "answer": "むりょう" },
        { "question": "charged / fee", "kanji_question": "有料", "answer": "ゆうりょう" },
        { "question": "plant", "kanji_question": "植物", "answer": "しょくぶつ" },
        { "question": "growth / to grow", "kanji_question": "成長", "answer": "せいちょう" },
        { "question": "suddenly", "kanji_question": "急に", "answer": "きゅうに" },
        { "question": "to fly out / to spring out / to run out", "kanji_question": "飛び出す", "answer": "とびだす" },
        { "question": "to fly", "kanji_question": "飛ぶ", "answer": "とぶ" },
        { "question": "to fly something / to throw", "kanji_question": "飛ばす", "answer": "とばす" },
        { "question": "seismic sea waves", "kanji_question": "津波", "answer": "つなみ" },
        { "question": "drinking / to drink", "kanji_question": "飲酒", "answer": "いんしゅ" },
        { "question": "prohibition of smoking / to quit smoking", "kanji_question": "禁煙", "answer": "きんえん" },
        { "question": "sales / amount", "kanji_question": "売上", "answer": "うりあげ" },
        { "question": "important", "kanji_question": "重要", "answer": "じゅうよう" },
        { "question": "legal adult", "kanji_question": "成年", "answer": "せいねん" },
        { "question": "minor (someone who is underage)", "kanji_question": "未成年", "answer": "みせいねん" },
        { "question": "stability / be stabilized / become stable", "kanji_question": "安定", "answer": "あんてい" },
        { "question": "to protect / to defend", "kanji_question": "守る", "answer": "まもる" },
        { "question": "bonus", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ボーナス" },
        { "question": "amount of money", "kanji_question": "金額", "answer": "きんがく" },
        { "question": "mechanical equipment and materials", "kanji_question": "機材", "answer": "きざい" },
        { "question": "production / to produce", "kanji_question": "生産", "answer": "せいさん" },
        { "question": "all", "kanji_question": "全て", "answer": "すべて" },
        { "question": "cooperation / to cooperate", "kanji_question": "協力", "answer": "きょうりょく" },
        { "question": "contest / large meeting", "kanji_question": "大会", "answer": "たいかい" },
        { "question": "design / to design", "kanji_question": "設計", "answer": "せっけい" },
        { "question": "old person", "kanji_question": "老人", "answer": "ろうじん" },
        { "question": "shoulder(s)", "kanji_question": "肩", "answer": "かた" },
        { "question": "recovery / to recover", "kanji_question": "回復", "answer": "かいふく" },
        { "question": "traffic jam / to be jammed up", "kanji_question": "渋滞", "answer": "じゅうたい" },
        { "question": "saving money / savings / to save money", "kanji_question": "貯金", "answer": "ちょきん" },
        { "question": "house rent / apartment rent", "kanji_question": "家賃", "answer": "やちん" },
        { "question": "security deposit (paid by the tenant to the landlord)", "kanji_question": "敷金", "answer": "しききん" },
        { "question": "key money (rewards paid by the tenant to the landlord)", "kanji_question": "礼金", "answer": "れいきん" },
        { "question": "service charge of an apartment", "kanji_question": "管理費", "answer": "かんりひ" },
        { "question": "scale", "kanji_question": "規模", "answer": "きぼ" },
        { "question": "layout of a house", "kanji_question": "間取り", "answer": "まどり" },
        { "question": "kitchen", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "キッチン" },
        { "question": "eat-in kitchen", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ダイニングキッチン" },
        { "question": "living room", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "リビング（ルーム）" },
        { "question": "entrance / entrance hall", "kanji_question": "玄関", "answer": "げんかん" },
        { "question": "veranda", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ベランダ" },
        { "question": "pet (animal)", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ペット" },
        { "question": "including / with", "kanji_question": "付き", "answer": "つき" },
        { "question": "(years) since construction", "kanji_question": "築", "answer": "ちく" },
        { "question": "property (real estate / possessions)", "kanji_question": "物件", "answer": "ぶっけん" },
        { "question": "going on foot", "kanji_question": "徒歩", "answer": "とほ" },
        { "question": "part", "kanji_question": "部分", "answer": "ぶぶん" },
        { "question": "whole", "kanji_question": "全体", "answer": "ぜんたい" }
    ],
    "N3L5VQuiz": [
        { "question": "responsibility", "kanji_question": "責任", "answer": "せきにん" },
        { "question": "deadline / due date", "kanji_question": "締め切り", "answer": "しめきり" },
        { "question": "day's program / schedule", "kanji_question": "日程", "answer": "にってい" },
        { "question": "lack / to be lacking", "kanji_question": "不足", "answer": "ふそく" },
        { "question": "existence / to exist", "kanji_question": "存在", "answer": "そんざい" },
        { "question": "frustrated / regrettable / upset", "kanji_question": "悔しい", "answer": "くやしい" },
        { "question": "noisy / annoying", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "うるさい" },
        { "question": "itchy", "kanji_question": "痒い", "answer": "かゆい" },
        { "question": "correspondence / communication / to correspond / to communicate", "kanji_question": "通信", "answer": "つうしん" },
        { "question": "homepage", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ホームページ" },
        { "question": "website", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ウェブサイト" },
        { "question": "to accumulate / to pile up", "kanji_question": "溜まる", "answer": "たまる" },
        { "question": "to accumulate something / to pile up something", "kanji_question": "溜める", "answer": "ためる" },
        { "question": "mysterious / strange / odd / miraculous", "kanji_question": "不思議", "answer": "ふしぎ" },
        { "question": "to get angry / to get offended", "kanji_question": "腹が立つ", "answer": "はらがたつ" },
        { "question": "actor", "kanji_question": "俳優", "answer": "はいゆう" },
        { "question": "actress", "kanji_question": "女優", "answer": "じょゆう" },
        { "question": "newcomer / new face", "kanji_question": "新人", "answer": "しんじん" },
        { "question": "theater company", "kanji_question": "劇団", "answer": "げきだん" },
        { "question": "entertainment", "kanji_question": "芸能", "answer": "げいのう" },
        { "question": "performer / celebrity", "kanji_question": "芸能人", "answer": "げいのうじん" },
        { "question": "play (drama)", "kanji_question": "芝居", "answer": "しばい" },
        { "question": "to be solved / to come untied", "kanji_question": "解ける", "answer": "とける" },
        { "question": "at any cost / by any means", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "どうしても" },
        { "question": "to decrease", "kanji_question": "減る", "answer": "へる" },
        { "question": "to decrease something", "kanji_question": "減らす", "answer": "へらす" },
        { "question": "to pick up", "kanji_question": "拾う", "answer": "ひろう" },
        { "question": "diet / to go on a diet", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ダイエット" },
        { "question": "festival", "kanji_question": "祭り", "answer": "まつり" },
        { "question": "sidewalk", "kanji_question": "歩道", "answer": "ほどう" },
        { "question": "mountain climbing / to climb a mountain", "kanji_question": "登山", "answer": "とざん" },
        { "question": "land", "kanji_question": "土地", "answer": "とち" },
        { "question": "bench", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ベンチ" },
        { "question": "trees and flowers", "kanji_question": "花木", "answer": "かぼく" },
        { "question": "creature", "kanji_question": "生物", "answer": "せいぶつ" },
        { "question": "product", "kanji_question": "製品", "answer": "せいひん" },
        { "question": "scratch / wound / injury / scar", "kanji_question": "傷", "answer": "きず" },
        { "question": "to get injured / to get hurt", "kanji_question": "傷つく", "answer": "きずつく" },
        { "question": "act of going somewhere without getting out of your vehicle", "kanji_question": "乗り入れ", "answer": "のりいれ" },
        { "question": "important points / precaution", "kanji_question": "注意事項", "answer": "ちゅういじこう" },
        { "question": "early / fast", "kanji_question": "早め", "answer": "はやめ" },
        { "question": "late / slow", "kanji_question": "遅め", "answer": "おそめ" },
        { "question": "agreement / understanding / to agree / to understand", "kanji_question": "納得", "answer": "なっとく" },
        { "question": "submission / to submit", "kanji_question": "提出", "answer": "ていしゅつ" },
        { "question": "various", "kanji_question": "色々", "answer": "いろいろ" },
        { "question": "to give up", "kanji_question": "諦める", "answer": "あきらめる" },
        { "question": "problem / point at issue", "kanji_question": "問題点", "answer": "もんだいてん" },
        { "question": "to explain / to discuss / to argue", "kanji_question": "論じる", "answer": "ろんじる" },
        { "question": "fireworks", "kanji_question": "花火", "answer": "はなび" },
        { "question": "pet owner", "kanji_question": "飼い主", "answer": "かいぬし" },
        { "question": "physical exercise / gymnastics", "kanji_question": "体操", "answer": "たいそう" },
        { "question": "empty can", "kanji_question": "空き缶", "answer": "あきかん" },
        { "question": "empty bottle", "kanji_question": "空き瓶", "answer": "あきびん" },
        { "question": "danger / dangerous", "kanji_question": "危険", "answer": "きけん" },
        { "question": "neglect / to leave something / to neglect something", "kanji_question": "放置", "answer": "ほうち" },
        { "question": "trouble / nuisance / to be troubled", "kanji_question": "迷惑", "answer": "めいわく" },
        { "question": "to let something go / to let something off", "kanji_question": "放す", "answer": "はなす" },
        { "question": "to let a pet or an animal run loose", "kanji_question": "放し飼い", "answer": "はなしがい" },
        { "question": "square / plaza / open space", "kanji_question": "広場", "answer": "ひろば" },
        { "question": "golf", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ゴルフ" },
        { "question": "roller skates / roller skating", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ローラースケート" },
        { "question": "kickboard / kickboarding", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "キックボード" },
        { "question": "skateboard / skateboarding", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "スケートボード" },
        { "question": "to try", "kanji_question": "試す", "answer": "ためす" },
        { "question": "wasteful", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "もったいない" },
        { "question": "phenomenon", "kanji_question": "現象", "answer": "げんしょう" },
        { "question": "string/cord", "kanji_question": "紐", "answer": "ひも" }
    ],
    "N3L6VQuiz": [
        { "question": "export / to export", "kanji_question": "輸出", "answer": "ゆしゅつ" },
        { "question": "import / to import", "kanji_question": "輸入", "answer": "ゆにゅう" },
        { "question": "export and import", "kanji_question": "輸出入", "answer": "ゆしゅつにゅう" },
        { "question": "on hand", "kanji_question": "手持ち", "answer": "てもち" },
        { "question": "my / our", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "わが" },
        { "question": "these (time)", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ここ" },
        { "question": "specially manufactured / to specially manufacture", "kanji_question": "特製", "answer": "とくせい" },
        { "question": "to indicate / to state / to describe", "kanji_question": "述べる", "answer": "のべる" },
        { "question": "dramatic / sudden", "kanji_question": "急激", "answer": "きゅうげき" },
        { "question": "most", "kanji_question": "最も", "answer": "もっとも" },
        { "question": "cause / factor", "kanji_question": "要因", "answer": "よういん" },
        { "question": "achievement", "kanji_question": "成果", "answer": "せいか" },
        { "question": "rise / to rise", "kanji_question": "上昇", "answer": "じょうしょう" },
        { "question": "decrease / to decrease", "kanji_question": "減少", "answer": "げんしょう" },
        { "question": "increase / to increase", "kanji_question": "増加", "answer": "ぞうか" },
        { "question": "strong yen", "kanji_question": "円高", "answer": "えんだか" },
        { "question": "weak yen", "kanji_question": "円安", "answer": "えんやす" },
        { "question": "attention / to pay attention", "kanji_question": "注目", "answer": "ちゅうもく" },
        { "question": "sum of money", "kanji_question": "総額", "answer": "そうがく" },
        { "question": "chart / list / table", "kanji_question": "表", "answer": "ひょう" },
        { "question": "diagram / chart / graph", "kanji_question": "図", "answer": "ず" },
        { "question": "cut / reduction / to reduce", "kanji_question": "削減", "answer": "さくげん" },
        { "question": "transparent", "kanji_question": "透明", "answer": "とうめい" },
        { "question": "brown", "kanji_question": "茶色", "answer": "ちゃいろ" },
        { "question": "time / period", "kanji_question": "時期", "answer": "じき" },
        { "question": "contract", "kanji_question": "契約", "answer": "けいやく" },
        { "question": "to tie / to unite / to connect / to make (a contract)", "kanji_question": "結ぶ", "answer": "むすぶ" },
        { "question": "Meiji", "kanji_question": "明治", "answer": "めいじ" },
        { "question": "Taisho", "kanji_question": "大正", "answer": "たいしょう" },
        { "question": "Showa", "kanji_question": "昭和", "answer": "しょうわ" },
        { "question": "Heisei", "kanji_question": "平成", "answer": "へいせい" },
        { "question": "analysis / to analyze", "kanji_question": "分析", "answer": "ぶんせき" },
        { "question": "new", "kanji_question": "新規", "answer": "しんき" },
        { "question": "partner", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "パートナー" },
        { "question": "amount", "kanji_question": "量", "answer": "りょう" },
        { "question": "mainstream", "kanji_question": "主流", "answer": "しゅりゅう" },
        { "question": "adjustment / to adjust", "kanji_question": "調整", "answer": "ちょうせい" },
        { "question": "detailed", "kanji_question": "詳しいい", "answer": "くわしい" },
        { "question": "each", "kanji_question": "各", "answer": "かく" },
        { "question": "reading / to read a book", "kanji_question": "読書", "answer": "どくしょ" },
        { "question": "activity / to act", "kanji_question": "活動", "answer": "かつどう" },
        { "question": "volunteer", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ボランティア" },
        { "question": "immediately / without stopping", "kanji_question": "一気に", "answer": "いっきに" },
        { "question": "fixed / constant", "kanji_question": "一定", "answer": "いってい" },
        { "question": "temporary", "kanji_question": "一時的", "answer": "いちじてき" },
        { "question": "gradually", "kanji_question": "徐々に", "answer": "じょじょに" },
        { "question": "large / substantial", "kanji_question": "大幅", "answer": "おおはば" },
        { "question": "more and more / increasingly", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ますます" },
        { "question": "instructions", "kanji_question": "説明書", "answer": "せつめいしょ" },
        { "question": "drug store", "kanji_question": "薬局", "answer": "やっきょく" },
        { "question": "disobedience / to disobey (a promise, rule)", "kanji_question": "違反", "answer": "いはん" },
        { "question": "consideration / to consider", "kanji_question": "検討", "answer": "けんとう" },
        { "question": "Japan and the US", "kanji_question": "日米", "answer": "にちべい" },
        { "question": "relation / to be related", "kanji_question": "関係", "answer": "かんけい" },
        { "question": "each other", "kanji_question": "互い", "answer": "たがい" },
        { "question": "one's weight", "kanji_question": "体重", "answer": "たいじゅう" },
        { "question": "one's height", "kanji_question": "身長", "answer": "しんちょう" },
        { "question": "residence / housing", "kanji_question": "住宅", "answer": "じゅうたく" },
        { "question": "teaching material", "kanji_question": "教材", "answer": "きょうざい" },
        { "question": "offer / provision / to offer / to provide", "kanji_question": "提供", "answer": "ていきょう" },
        { "question": "rate / ratio", "kanji_question": "割合", "answer": "わりあい" },
        { "question": "to occupy / to hold / to rank / to account for", "kanji_question": "占める", "answer": "しめる" },
        { "question": "consumption tax", "kanji_question": "消費税", "answer": "しょうひぜい" },
        { "question": "tax", "kanji_question": "税金", "answer": "ぜいきん" },
        { "question": "saving / to save (money, water, electricity, etc.)", "kanji_question": "節約", "answer": "せつやく" },
        { "question": "industry", "kanji_question": "業界", "answer": "ぎょうかい" }
    ],
    "N3L7VQuiz": [
        { "question": "to refuse / to turn down", "kanji_question": "断る", "answer": "ことわる" },
        { "question": "simultaneously / the same time", "kanji_question": "同時", "answer": "どうじ" },
        { "question": "sports field", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "グラウンド" },
        { "question": "counter for laps, circuits or rounds", "kanji_question": "周", "answer": "しゅう" },
        { "question": "position / situation", "kanji_question": "立場", "answer": "たちば" },
        { "question": "point of view", "kanji_question": "視点", "answer": "してん" },
        { "question": "present condition / status", "kanji_question": "現状", "answer": "げんじょう" },
        { "question": "misunderstanding / to misunderstand", "kanji_question": "誤解", "answer": "ごかい" },
        { "question": "secretary", "kanji_question": "秘書", "answer": "ひしょ" },
        { "question": "executive secretary / coordinator", "kanji_question": "幹事", "answer": "かんじ" },
        { "question": "change / to change / to transfer", "kanji_question": "異動", "answer": "いどう" },
        { "question": "musician", "kanji_question": "音楽家", "answer": "おんがくか" },
        { "question": "singer", "kanji_question": "歌手", "answer": "かしゅ" },
        { "question": "reason / cause", "kanji_question": "訳", "answer": "わけ" },
        { "question": "employment / to find employment", "kanji_question": "就職", "answer": "しゅうしょく" },
        { "question": "professional", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "プロ" },
        { "question": "challenge / to challenge", "kanji_question": "挑戦", "answer": "ちょうせん" },
        { "question": "father", "kanji_question": "父親", "answer": "ちちおや" },
        { "question": "mother", "kanji_question": "母親", "answer": "ははおや" },
        { "question": "guidance / coaching / to guide / to coach / to instruct", "kanji_question": "指導", "answer": "しどう" },
        { "question": "value", "kanji_question": "価値", "answer": "かち" },
        { "question": "opposition / opposite / to reverse", "kanji_question": "反対", "answer": "はんたい" },
        { "question": "hardship / to go through hardship", "kanji_question": "苦労", "answer": "くろう" },
        { "question": "suddenly", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "いきなり" },
        { "question": "thoughts / ideas", "kanji_question": "考え", "answer": "かんがえ" },
        { "question": "will / intent", "kanji_question": "意志", "answer": "いし" },
        { "question": "sense / feeling", "kanji_question": "感覚", "answer": "かんかく" },
        { "question": "postcard", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "はがき" },
        { "question": "membership fee", "kanji_question": "会費", "answer": "かいひ" },
        { "question": "tuition", "kanji_question": "学費", "answer": "がくひ" },
        { "question": "aroma", "kanji_question": "香り", "answer": "かおり" },
        { "question": "Dear Sir / Madam (written in a letter)", "kanji_question": "拝啓", "answer": "はいけい" },
        { "question": "Sincerely yours (written in a letter)", "kanji_question": "敬具", "answer": "けいぐ" },
        { "question": "passage of time / to pass", "kanji_question": "経過", "answer": "けいか" },
        { "question": "production / to produce", "kanji_question": "制作", "answer": "せいさく" },
        { "question": "local", "kanji_question": "地元", "answer": "じもと" },
        { "question": "studio / workshop", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "アトリエ" },
        { "question": "word", "kanji_question": "言葉", "answer": "ことば" },
        { "question": "to visit", "kanji_question": "訪れる", "answer": "おとずれる" },
        { "question": "to strive", "kanji_question": "励む", "answer": "はげむ" },
        { "question": "to encourage", "kanji_question": "励ます", "answer": "はげます" },
        { "question": "hectic / dizzy", "kanji_question": "目まぐるしい", "answer": "めまぐるしい" },
        { "question": "new semester", "kanji_question": "新学期", "answer": "しんがっき" },
        { "question": "to endeavor / to devote", "kanji_question": "勤しむ", "answer": "いそしむ" },
        { "question": "condition / state", "kanji_question": "具合", "answer": "ぐあい" },
        { "question": "construction / to construct / to establish", "kanji_question": "建設", "answer": "けんせつ" },
        { "question": "regret / to regret", "kanji_question": "後悔", "answer": "こうかい" },
        { "question": "separation / farewell", "kanji_question": "別れ", "answer": "わかれ" },
        { "question": "helpless / hopeless", "kanji_question": "心細い", "answer": "こころぼそい" },
        { "question": "reassuring", "kanji_question": "心強い", "answer": "こころづよい" },
        { "question": "summer heat fatigue", "kanji_question": "夏バテ", "answer": "なつばて" },
        { "question": "early summer", "kanji_question": "初夏", "answer": "しょか" },
        { "question": "New Year", "kanji_question": "新春", "answer": "しんしゅん" },
        { "question": "one's superior", "kanji_question": "目上", "answer": "めうえ" },
        { "question": "the economy / business conditions", "kanji_question": "景気", "answer": "けいき" },
        { "question": "a request / to request", "kanji_question": "要求", "answer": "ようきゅう" },
        { "question": "hope / wish / to hope / to wish", "kanji_question": "希望", "answer": "きぼう" },
        { "question": "at least", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "せめて" },
        { "question": "staying up late / to stay up late", "kanji_question": "夜ふかし", "answer": "よふかし" },
        { "question": "very / quite", "kanji_question": "随分", "answer": "ずいぶん" },
        { "question": "calendar", "kanji_question": "暦", "answer": "こよみ" }
    ],
    "N3L8VQuiz": [
        { "question": "trouble", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "トラブル" },
        { "question": "science", "kanji_question": "科学", "answer": "かがく" },
        { "question": "the present time / at present", "kanji_question": "現在", "answer": "げんざい" },
        { "question": "to follow / to obey", "kanji_question": "従う", "answer": "したがう" },
        { "question": "to finish / to result in something / to be settled", "kanji_question": "済む", "answer": "すむ" },
        { "question": "expressly / on purpose", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "わざわざ" },
        { "question": "fortunate / fortunately", "kanji_question": "幸い", "answer": "さいわい" },
        { "question": "unfortunate / unfortunately", "kanji_question": "不幸", "answer": "ふこう" },
        { "question": "your company (honorific expression)", "kanji_question": "御社", "answer": "おんしゃ" },
        { "question": "lose / to lose (profits)", "kanji_question": "損失", "answer": "そんしつ" },
        { "question": "to summon / to beckon / to invite / to bring about", "kanji_question": "招く", "answer": "まねく" },
        { "question": "item / matter", "kanji_question": "案件", "answer": "あんけん" },
        { "question": "inventory / stock", "kanji_question": "在庫", "answer": "ざいこ" },
        { "question": "shipping / to ship", "kanji_question": "発送", "answer": "はっそう" },
        { "question": "order / to order", "kanji_question": "発注", "answer": "はっちゅう" },
        { "question": "(even) under normal circumstances / in addition to", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ただでさえ" },
        { "question": "re~ / again", "kanji_question": "再", "answer": "さい" },
        { "question": "discount / to discount", "kanji_question": "割引", "answer": "わりびき" },
        { "question": "customer / client (company)", "kanji_question": "取引先", "answer": "とりひきさき" },
        { "question": "neatly / precisely", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "きちんと" },
        { "question": "to forgive", "kanji_question": "許す", "answer": "ゆるす" },
        { "question": "apology", "kanji_question": "詫び", "answer": "わび" },
        { "question": "correspondence / to correspond / to deal with", "kanji_question": "対応", "answer": "たいおう" },
        { "question": "large size / large-sized", "kanji_question": "大型", "answer": "おおがた" },
        { "question": "small size / small-sized", "kanji_question": "小型", "answer": "こがた" },
        { "question": "to dislike", "kanji_question": "嫌う", "answer": "きらう" },
        { "question": "investigation / inquiry / research / to investigate / to inquire / to examine", "kanji_question": "調査", "answer": "ちょうさ" },
        { "question": "school commute / to commute to school", "kanji_question": "通学", "answer": "つうがく" },
        { "question": "work commute / to commute to work", "kanji_question": "通勤", "answer": "つうきん" },
        { "question": "specialist / expert", "kanji_question": "専門家", "answer": "せんもんか" },
        { "question": "personal information", "kanji_question": "個人情報", "answer": "こじんじょうほう" },
        { "question": "serious / important", "kanji_question": "重大", "answer": "じゅうだい" },
        { "question": "average year / every year", "kanji_question": "例年", "answer": "れいねん" },
        { "question": "thanks / gratitude / to thank", "kanji_question": "感謝", "answer": "かんしゃ" },
        { "question": "interest / concern", "kanji_question": "関心", "answer": "かんしん" },
        { "question": "eastern-central area of Japan's main island", "kanji_question": "関東", "answer": "かんとう" },
        { "question": "western-central area of Japan's main island", "kanji_question": "関西", "answer": "かんさい" },
        { "question": "Japan's third biggest island, located southwest of the main island", "kanji_question": "九州", "answer": "きゅうしゅう" },
        { "question": "love / affection", "kanji_question": "愛情", "answer": "あいじょう" },
        { "question": "contact (from someone) / whereabouts / news", "kanji_question": "消息", "answer": "しょうそく" },
        { "question": "to pray / to wish", "kanji_question": "祈る", "answer": "いのる" },
        { "question": "safety / peace / safely / peaceful", "kanji_question": "無事", "answer": "ぶじ" },
        { "question": "to examine (medically)", "kanji_question": "診る", "answer": "みる" },
        { "question": "medical examination / to examine", "kanji_question": "診察", "answer": "しんさつ" },
        { "question": "aggressive attitude / confident / assured / firm", "kanji_question": "強気", "answer": "つよき" },
        { "question": "timid / weak", "kanji_question": "弱気", "answer": "よわき" },
        { "question": "one's own convenience / one's own way / selfish / self-willed", "kanji_question": "勝手", "answer": "かって" },
        { "question": "behavior / action / to take action", "kanji_question": "行動", "answer": "こうどう" },
        { "question": "mud", "kanji_question": "泥", "answer": "どろ" },
        { "question": "dust", "kanji_question": "埃", "answer": "ほこり" },
        { "question": "debt", "kanji_question": "借金", "answer": "しゃっきん" },
        { "question": "the whole body", "kanji_question": "全身", "answer": "ぜんしん" },
        { "question": "deterioration / to deteriorate / to get worse", "kanji_question": "悪化", "answer": "あっか" },
        { "question": "to give birth", "kanji_question": "産む", "answer": "うむ" },
        { "question": "decrease in the number of children", "kanji_question": "少子化", "answer": "しょうしか" },
        { "question": "serious / severe", "kanji_question": "深刻", "answer": "しんこく" },
        { "question": "nerves", "kanji_question": "神経", "answer": "しんけい" },
        { "question": "motor nerves / one's athletic ability", "kanji_question": "運動神経", "answer": "うんどうしんけい" },
        { "question": "body", "kanji_question": "身体", "answer": "しんたい" },
        { "question": "physical condition", "kanji_question": "体調", "answer": "たいちょう" },
        { "question": "inquiry", "kanji_question": "問い合わせ", "answer": "といあわせ" },
        { "question": "reply / answer / to reply / to answer", "kanji_question": "回答", "answer": "かいとう" },
        { "question": "designation / to appoint / to specify / to designate", "kanji_question": "指定", "answer": "してい" },
        { "question": "fixed date / due date", "kanji_question": "期日", "answer": "きじつ" },
        { "question": "about / approximately", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "およそ" },
        { "question": "tension / to be tense / to be nervous", "kanji_question": "緊張", "answer": "きんちょう" },
        { "question": "improvement / to improve", "kanji_question": "改善", "answer": "かいぜん" }
    ],
    "N3L9VQuiz": [
        { "question": "nature", "kanji_question": "自然", "answer": "しぜん" },
        { "question": "landscape", "kanji_question": "景観", "answer": "けいかん" },
        { "question": "to be blessed", "kanji_question": "恵まれる", "answer": "めぐまれる" },
        { "question": "river banks", "kanji_question": "両岸", "answer": "りょうがん" },
        { "question": "impression", "kanji_question": "印象", "answer": "いんしょう" },
        { "question": "elephant", "kanji_question": "像", "answer": "ぞう" },
        { "question": "horse", "kanji_question": "馬", "answer": "うま" },
        { "question": "shape / form / figure", "kanji_question": "形", "answer": "かたち" },
        { "question": "rare / unique", "kanji_question": "珍しい", "answer": "めずらしい" },
        { "question": "rock", "kanji_question": "岩", "answer": "いわ" },
        { "question": "rocky mountain", "kanji_question": "岩山", "answer": "いわやま" },
        { "question": "detailed / accurate", "kanji_question": "詳しい", "answer": "くわしい" },
        { "question": "lecture / speech / to lecture / to make a speech", "kanji_question": "講演", "answer": "こうえん" },
        { "question": "home (in your hometown)", "kanji_question": "実家", "answer": "じっか" },
        { "question": "to count", "kanji_question": "数える", "answer": "かぞえる" },
        { "question": "quantity", "kanji_question": "数量", "answer": "すうりょう" },
        { "question": "number", "kanji_question": "数字", "answer": "すうじ" },
        { "question": "number of people", "kanji_question": "人数", "answer": "にんずう" },
        { "question": "to roll / to lie around / thundering", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ごろごろ" },
        { "question": "someone else", "kanji_question": "別人", "answer": "べつじん" },
        { "question": "acquisition / to acquire", "kanji_question": "取得", "answer": "しゅとく" },
        { "question": "sold out / to be sold out", "kanji_question": "完売", "answer": "かんばい" },
        { "question": "after school", "kanji_question": "放課後", "answer": "ほうかご" },
        { "question": "club activity", "kanji_question": "部活", "answer": "ぶかつ" },
        { "question": "to grow / to raise / to rear", "kanji_question": "育てる", "answer": "そだてる" },
        { "question": "committee", "kanji_question": "委員会", "answer": "いいんかい" },
        { "question": "as ever", "kanji_question": "相変わらず", "answer": "あいかわらず" },
        { "question": "good listener", "kanji_question": "聞き上手", "answer": "ききじょうず" },
        { "question": "just recently / unintentionally", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "つい" },
        { "question": "finally / at last", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ついに" },
        { "question": "jealous", "kanji_question": "羨ましい", "answer": "うらやましい" },
        { "question": "fashionable / to be in fashion", "kanji_question": "流行", "answer": "りゅうこう" },
        { "question": "splendid / fine / grand", "kanji_question": "立派", "answer": "りっぱ" },
        { "question": "understanding / to understand", "kanji_question": "理解", "answer": "りかい" },
        { "question": "mistake", "kanji_question": "間違い", "answer": "まちがい" },
        { "question": "imitation / behavior / to imitate / to mimic / to copy", "kanji_question": "真似", "answer": "まね" },
        { "question": "fashion", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ファッション" },
        { "question": "contents / details", "kanji_question": "内容", "answer": "ないよう" },
        { "question": "contents / interior", "kanji_question": "中身", "answer": "なかみ" },
        { "question": "fierce / intense / violent / strong", "kanji_question": "激しい", "answer": "はげしい" },
        { "question": "to save / to rescue", "kanji_question": "救う", "answer": "すくう" },
        { "question": "to excel / to be better than", "kanji_question": "優れる", "answer": "すぐれる" },
        { "question": "claim / bill / to claim / to bill", "kanji_question": "請求", "answer": "せいきゅう" },
        { "question": "existence / to exist", "kanji_question": "存在", "answer": "そんざい" },
        { "question": "stay / to stay", "kanji_question": "滞在", "answer": "たいざい" },
        { "question": "status (social)", "kanji_question": "地位", "answer": "ちい" },
        { "question": "blood", "kanji_question": "血", "answer": "ち" },
        { "question": "long term", "kanji_question": "長期", "answer": "ちょうき" },
        { "question": "short term", "kanji_question": "短期", "answer": "たんき" },
        { "question": "degree / amount", "kanji_question": "程度", "answer": "ていど" },
        { "question": "pot", "kanji_question": "鍋", "answer": "なべ" },
        { "question": "wave", "kanji_question": "波", "answer": "なみ" },
        { "question": "purpose", "kanji_question": "目的", "answer": "もくてき" },
        { "question": "letter / character", "kanji_question": "文字", "answer": "もじ" },
        { "question": "frustrating / to be frustrated", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "いらいら" },
        { "question": "more and more / finally / really", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "いよいよ" },
        { "question": "natural / reasonable / naturally / justly", "kanji_question": "当然", "answer": "とうぜん" },
        { "question": "plain / simple", "kanji_question": "地味", "answer": "じみ" },
        { "question": "to decide", "kanji_question": "決まる", "answer": "きまる" },
        { "question": "to decide (something)", "kanji_question": "決める", "answer": "きめる" },
        { "question": "all the members", "kanji_question": "全員", "answer": "ぜんいん" },
        { "question": "sudden / unexpected / suddenly / unexpectedly", "kanji_question": "突然", "answer": "とつぜん" },
        { "question": "bachelor / unmarried", "kanji_question": "独身", "answer": "どくしん" }
    ],
    "N3L10VQuiz": [
        { "question": "to pass / to lapse (time)", "kanji_question": "経つ", "answer": "たつ" },
        { "question": "swing / behavior / pretense", "kanji_question": "振り", "answer": "ふり" },
        { "question": "driving / to drive", "kanji_question": "運転", "answer": "うんてん" },
        { "question": "an accident resulting in injury or death", "kanji_question": "人身事故", "answer": "じんしんじこ" },
        { "question": "to exchange glances / to compare / to postpone", "kanji_question": "見合わせる", "answer": "みあわせる" },
        { "question": "to be in a hurry / to be impatient", "kanji_question": "焦る", "answer": "あせる" },
        { "question": "selfishness / selfish", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "わがまま" },
        { "question": "slowly", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ゆっくり" },
        { "question": "serious", "kanji_question": "真剣", "answer": "しんけん" },
        { "question": "to scold", "kanji_question": "叱る", "answer": "しかる" },
        { "question": "progress / to progress", "kanji_question": "進歩", "answer": "しんぽ" },
        { "question": "(Japanese) flower arrangement", "kanji_question": "生け花", "answer": "いけばな" },
        { "question": "complaint", "kanji_question": "文句", "answer": "もんく" },
        { "question": "insult / vilification", "kanji_question": "悪口", "answer": "わるぐち" },
        { "question": "as expected", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "さすが" },
        { "question": "please", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "どうか" },
        { "question": "criminal / culprit", "kanji_question": "犯人", "answer": "はんにん" },
        { "question": "case / incident", "kanji_question": "事件", "answer": "じけん" },
        { "question": "escape / to escape", "kanji_question": "逃走", "answer": "とうそう" },
        { "question": "to suit", "kanji_question": "似合う", "answer": "にあう" },
        { "question": "to talk / to chat / to speak", "kanji_question": "喋る", "answer": "しゃべる" },
        { "question": "confidence", "kanji_question": "自信", "answer": "じしん" },
        { "question": "ordinal number", "kanji_question": "第", "answer": "だい" },
        { "question": "doctorate / PhD / doctor / expert", "kanji_question": "博士", "answer": "はくし" },
        { "question": "master's degree", "kanji_question": "修士", "answer": "しゅうし" },
        { "question": "bachelor's degree", "kanji_question": "学士", "answer": "がくし" },
        { "question": "universe / outer space", "kanji_question": "宇宙", "answer": "うちゅう" },
        { "question": "nation / citizen", "kanji_question": "国民", "answer": "こくみん" },
        { "question": "life", "kanji_question": "生命", "answer": "せいめい" },
        { "question": "the public / general / ordinary / public", "kanji_question": "一般", "answer": "いっぱん" },
        { "question": "common sense", "kanji_question": "常識", "answer": "じょうしき" },
        { "question": "personal expenses / labor costs", "kanji_question": "人件費", "answer": "じんけんひ" },
        { "question": "Southeast Asia", "kanji_question": "東南アジア", "answer": "とうなんあじあ" },
        { "question": "East Asia", "kanji_question": "東アジア", "answer": "ひがしあじあ" },
        { "question": "attitude", "kanji_question": "態度", "answer": "たいど" },
        { "question": "to lose weight / to get thin", "kanji_question": "痩せる", "answer": "やせる" },
        { "question": "to gain weight / to grow fat", "kanji_question": "太る", "answer": "ふとる" },
        { "question": "action / movement", "kanji_question": "動作", "answer": "どうさ" },
        { "question": "individuality / one's personality", "kanji_question": "個性", "answer": "こせい" },
        { "question": "reference / search / to look up / to search", "kanji_question": "検索", "answer": "けんさく" },
        { "question": "video", "kanji_question": "動画", "answer": "どうが" },
        { "question": "ball / drop / gem", "kanji_question": "玉", "answer": "たま" },
        { "question": "Japanese ball and cup game", "kanji_question": "けん玉", "answer": "けんだま" },
        { "question": "imagination / to imagine", "kanji_question": "想像", "answer": "そうぞう" },
        { "question": "from now on", "kanji_question": "今後", "answer": "こんご" },
        { "question": "an expectation / to expect", "kanji_question": "期待", "answer": "きたい" },
        { "question": "an idea / to come up with (an idea)", "kanji_question": "発想", "answer": "はっそう" },
        { "question": "evolution / to evolve", "kanji_question": "進化", "answer": "しんか" },
        { "question": "modern era / nowadays", "kanji_question": "現代", "answer": "げんだい" },
        { "question": "recent years", "kanji_question": "近年", "answer": "きんねん" },
        { "question": "boom / fad", "kanji_question": "", "answer": "ブーム" },
        { "question": "article / news story", "kanji_question": "記事", "answer": "きじ" },
        { "question": "to battle / to fight", "kanji_question": "戦う", "answer": "たたかう" },
        { "question": "to strike / to hit / to be correct (with a prediction) / to win (in a lottery or a raffle)", "kanji_question": "当たる", "answer": "あたる" },
        { "question": "to hit (the target) / to expose / to put something to", "kanji_question": "当てる", "answer": "あてる" },
        { "question": "to take (a shower) / to bathe / to be exposed to", "kanji_question": "浴びる", "answer": "あびる" },
        { "question": "major (field of study)", "kanji_question": "専攻", "answer": "せんこう" },
        { "question": "noise / din", "kanji_question": "騒音", "answer": "そうおん" },
        { "question": "to pour", "kanji_question": "注ぐ", "answer": "そそぐ" },
        { "question": "ideal", "kanji_question": "理想", "answer": "りそう" },
        { "question": "start / commencement / to start / to commence", "kanji_question": "開始", "answer": "かいし" },
        { "question": "resolution / determination / to make up one's mind / to determine", "kanji_question": "決心", "answer": "けっしん" },
        { "question": "honesty / honest", "kanji_question": "正直", "answer": "しょうじき" },
        { "question": "humanity", "kanji_question": "人類", "answer": "じんるい" },
        { "question": "health / energy / condition", "kanji_question": "調子", "answer": "ちょうし" },
        { "question": "climax", "kanji_question": "盛り上がり", "answer": "もりあがり" },
        { "question": "young people", "kanji_question": "若者", "answer": "わかもの" }
    ]
}
